About Me

I am a web developer specialising in front-end development and UX/UI design. I love the process of creating innovative and performant applications that add value to people's lives. This passion has propelled me to learn a vast range of technologies with the aim of creating solutions to difficult problems.

Languages

- JavaScript
- · HTML & CSS
- React JS
- Node JS

Tools & Skills

- Node Package Manager
- Git/Git Workflow
- Sass
- Bootstrap

Interests

- Travelling
- Weight Training & Calisthenics
- Reading Books
- Cooking

Contact

Email:

mohamadfaruk@live.com

Website:

http://www.mohamadfaruk.com/

Mohamad Faruk

Web Developer

Based in London, UK

Work Experience

May 2021 - present

Freelance Web Developer

Designed modern accessible websites utilising HTML, Sass and JavaScript. Applied structure to the webpage using a CSS framework, Bootstrap.

March 2020 - present

Case Coordinator

Nursing & Midwifery Council

Manage and process cases & complex legal documentation in accordance with regulatory law, whilst complying to GDPR principles.

January 2016 - January 2017

Job Support Advisor

Attend ABI

Support clients in their return to employment by holding regular face-to-face discussions, source prospective employment opportunities and checking clients employment documents.

Education

2020 Zero to Mastery Academy
present Self led web development framework

2014 BSc (Hons) Pychology
University of Westminster

Achieved an upper second class honours.

2011 Extended Diploma in ICT

2013 City and Islington College

Achieved a triple distinction (equivalent to three A's in A levels).

2004 GCSE's

2009 William Ellis Secondary School

Obtained 9 A - C's in various subjects including Maths, Science and English.